{
    "subject": "resource/Urmia_Khanate",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Urmia",
    "human_readable": "The capital of Urmia Khanate is Urmia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9881424307823181,
            "question": "Is Urmia the capital of the Urmia Khanate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9818356037139893,
            "question": "What city was the capital of the Urmia Khanate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9582411646842957,
            "question": "What is the name of the Khanate that had Urmia as its capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.817310631275177,
            "question": "Where was the Urmia Khanate located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6560550332069397,
            "question": "Who ruled the Urmia Khanate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5484387278556824,
            "question": "What is the significance of the Urmia Khanate in history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47521913051605225,
            "question": "What are some notable events that happened during the rule of the Urmia Khanate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47235429286956787,
            "question": "When did the Urmia Khanate exist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4349301755428314,
            "question": "What was the culture like during the rule of the Urmia Khanate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3593956530094147,
            "question": "How did the Urmia Khanate interact with other neighboring powers?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of Urmia Khanate is Urmia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8759_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the culture like during the rule of the Urmia Khanate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8759_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did the Urmia Khanate exist?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8759_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some notable events that happened during the rule of the Urmia Khanate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8759_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8759_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8759_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8759_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8759_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8759_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8759_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8759_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8759_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8759_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8759_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the context information, specifically file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8759/re-ranker-msmarco/11.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8759/re-ranker-msmarco/7.txt, the city of Urmia was indeed the capital of the Urmia Khanate from 1747 to 1865."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that the city of Urmia served as the capital of the Urmia Khanate from 1747 to 1865, which supports the statement \"The capital of Urmia Khanate is Urmia.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}